RG 009, Office of the Attorney General
Connecticut State Library
- Series 1. Correspondence, 1899-1947
  - 1937-1940
    - K (Miscellaneous), 1939-1940 (Box 7)
    - L (Miscellaneous), 1940 (Box 7)
    - Labor and Factory Inspection, 1937-1940 (Box 7)
    - Library, State, 1937-1939 (Box 7)
    - Liquor Control Commission, 1937-1940 (Box 7)
    - Long Lane Farm, 1937-1939 (Box 8)
    - M (Miscellaneous), 1934-1939 (Box 8)
    - Mansfield State Training School & Hospital, 1936-1939 (Box 8)
    - Medical Examining Board, 1936-1937 (Box 8)
    - Milk Administration, 1937-1940 (Box 8)
    - Motor Vehicle Dept., 1937-1940 (Box 8)
    - N (Miscellaneous), 1939-1940 (Box 8)
    - Natureopathic, Board of, 1937-1940 (Box 8)
    - Norwich State Hospital, 1937-1940 (Box 8)
    - Nurses, Board of Examiners of, 1937-1940 (Box 8)
    - O (Miscellaneous), 1938-1939 (Box 8)
    - Old Age Assistance Tax, 1937-1940 (Box 8)
    - Opticians Commission, 1937-1940 (Box 8)
    - Optometry, State Board of Examiners, 1937-1939 (Box 8)
    - Osteopathy, 1936-1937 (Box 8)
    - P (Miscellaneous), 1940 (Box 8)
    - Park and Forest Commission, State, 1937-1940 (Box 8)
    - Personnel Committee, 1944 (Box 8)
    - Personnel Director, 1937-1940 (Box 8)
    - Pharmacy Commission, 1937-1939 (Box 8)
    - Police Association, State, 1937 (Box 8)
    - Police Department, State, 1937-1940 (Box 8)
    - Public Records Examiners, 1937-1940 (Box 8)
    - Public Utilities Commission, 1937-1940 (Box 8)
    - Public Welfare Council, State, 1937-1940 (Box 8)
    - Public Works Commissioner, 1937-1939 (Box 8)
    - Purchasing Agent, 1937-1939 (Box 8)
    - Q (Miscellaneous), 1937 (Box 8)
    - R (Miscellaneous), 1938-1940 (Box 8)
    - Reconstruction Finance Corp., 1937 (Box 8)
    - Retirement commission, 1939-1940 (Box 8)
    - Rivers, Harbors and Bridges, Commissioner, 1937-1938 (Box 8)
    - S (Miscellaneous), 1937-1940 (Box 8)
    - School Fund, 1937-1940 (Box 8)
    - Secretary of State, 1937-1940 (Box 8)
    - Selectmen, 1937-1940 (Box 8)
    - Shell Fish Commission, 1937-1940 (Box 8)
    - Sheriff, 1937-1940 (Box 9)
    - Soldiers, Sailors, and Marines Fund Matter, 1937-1939 (Box 9)
    - Southbury Training School, 1940 (Box 9)
    - State Board of Civil Engineer, 1937-1938 (Box 9)
    - State Revision Commission, 1938 (Box 9)
    - Tax Commissioner, 1937-1940 (Box 9)
    - Teacher’s Retirement Board, 1935-1940 (Box 9)
    - Town Clerks, 1938-1940 (Box 9)
    - Traffic Commission (State), 1938-1940 (Box 9)
    - Treasurer, State, 1936-1940 (Box 9)
    - Tuberculosis Commission (State), 1938-1940 (Box 9)
    - U (Miscellaneous), 1939 (Box 9)
    - United States Government, 1935-1940 (Box 9)
    - University of Connecticut, 1937-1941 (Box 9)
    - Veterans Fund, 1937-1938 (Box 9)
    - Veterans Home Commission, 1937-1939 (Box 9)
    - Voting, 1937-1940 (Box 9)
    - W (Miscellaneous), 1937-1940 (Box 9)
    - Water Commission, 1938-1940 (Box 9)
    - Welfare Department, 1936-1940 (Box 9)
  - 1941
    - Accountancy Board, State, 1941 (Box 10)
    - Adjutant General, 1941 (Box 10)
    - Aeronautics, Commission, 1941 (Box 10)
    - Agriculture Department (Conn.), 1941 (Box 10)
    - Attorney General, 1941 (Box 10)
    - Attorneys General Convention, 1941 (Box 10)
    - Auditors, State, 1941 (Box 10)
    - B (Miscellaneous), 1941 (Box 10)
    - Bank Commissioner, 1941 (Box 10)
    - Blind, 1941 (Box 10)
    - C (Miscellaneous), 1941 (Box 10)
    - Cancellations & Compromises (Not Welfare), 1939-1941 (Box 10)
    - Comptroller, 1941 (Box 10)
    - Connecticut Council for National Defense, 1941 (Box 10)
    - Connecticut Regional Market Authority, 1941 (Box 10)
    - Connecticut State Farm For Women, 1941 (Box 10)
    - Connecticut State Hospital, 1941 (Box 10)
    - D (Miscellaneous), 1941 (Box 10)
    - Dairy & Food Commission, 1941 (Box 10)
    - Dental Commission, 1941 (Box 10)
    - Domestic Animals, Conn., 1941 (Box 10)
    - Education, Board of, 1940-1941 (Box 10)
    - Election, 1941 (Box 10)
    - Fairfield State Hospital, 1941 (Box 10)
    - Fish & Game Commission, 1940-1941 (Box 10)
    - Fitch’s Home for Soldiers, 1940-1941 (Box 10)
    - Flood Control and Water Policy Commission, 1941 (Box 10)
    - General Assembly, 1941 (Box 10)
    - Governor, 1941 (Box 10)
    - H (Miscellaneous), 1941 (Box 10)
    - Health Department, 1941 (Box 10)
    - Highway Department, 1941 (Box 10)
    - Highway Department, 1941 (Box 10)
    - I (Miscellaneous), 1941 (Box 10)
    - Insurance Department, 1941 (Box 10)
    - Interstate Sanitation Commission (Tristate Commission), 1938-1941 (Box 10)
    - J (Miscellaneous), 1941 (Box 10)
    - Judiciary Dept., 1941 (Box 10)
    - L (Miscellaneous), 1941 (Box 10)
    - Labor and Factory Inspection, 1941 (Box 10)
    - Library, 1941 (Box 10)
    - Liquor Control Commission., 1941 (Box 10)
    - Long Lane Farm, 1941 (Box 10)
    - M (Miscellaneous), 1941 (Box 11)
    - Mansfield State Training School, 1941 (Box 11)
    - Mc (Miscellaneous), 1941 (Box 11)
    - Medical Examination Board Connecticut, 1941 (Box 11)
    - Milk Administration, 1941-1942 (Box 11)
    - Motor Vehicle Department, 1941 (Box 11)
    - N (Miscellaneous), 1941 (Box 11)
    - National Defense - Washington, 1941 (Box 11)
    - Natureopathic, Board of, 1941 (Box 11)
    - Norwich State Hospital, 1941 (Box 11)
    - O (Miscellaneous), 1941 (Box 11)
    - Opticians Commissions, 1941 (Box 11)
    - P (Miscellaneous), 1941 (Box 11)
    - Park & Forest Commission, 1941 (Box 11)
    - Personnel Director, 1941 (Box 11)
    - Pharmacy, 1941 (Box 11)
    - Police Department, State, 1941 (Box 11)
    - Prison Association, Connecticut, 1941 (Box 11)
    - Public Utilities Commission, 1941 (Box 11)
    - Public Works Commission, 1941 (Box 11)
    - Purchasing Agent, 1941 (Box 11)
    - Retirement Commission, 1940 (Box 11)
    - S (Miscellaneous), 1941 (Box 11)
    - Secretary of State, 1941 (Box 11)
    - Selective Service, 1941 (Box 11)
    - Selectman, 1941 (Box 11)
    - Southbury Training School, 1940 (Box 11)
    - Steamship Terminals, Commissioners of, 1941-1943 (Box 11)
    - T (Miscellaneous), 1941 (Box 11)
    - Tax Commissioner, 1941 (Box 11)
    - Teachers" Retirement Board, 1941 (Box 11)
    - Town Clerk, 1941 (Box 11)
    - Traffic Commission, State, 1941 (Box 11)
    - Treasurer, State, 1941 (Box 11)
    - Tuberculosis Commission, State, 1941 (Box 11)
    - U (Miscellaneous), 1941 (Box 11)
    - Unemployment Compensation, 1941 (Box 11)
    - United States Government, 1931-1942 (Box 11)
    - University of Connecticut, 1939-1941 (Box 11)
    - Veterans Home Commission, 1941 (Box 11)
    - Voting, 1941 (Box 11)
    - W (Miscellaneous), 1941 (Box 11)
    - Water Commission, 1941 (Box 11)
    - Welfare Department, 1941 (Box 11)
    - X-Z, 1941 (Box 11)
  - 1942
    - A (Miscellaneous), 1942 (Box 12)
    - Adjutant General, 1942 (Box 12)
    - Advisory Personnel Commission, 1942 (Box 12)
    - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1942 (Box 12)
    - Agriculture, Department of, 1942 (Box 12)
    - American Legion - Soldiers, Sailors & Marine Funds, 1942 (Box 12)
    - Attorney General Convention, 1942 (Box 12)
    - Attorneys General of Other States, 1942 (Box 12)
    - Auditors, State, 1942 (Box 12)
    - B (Miscellaneous), 1942 (Box 12)
    - Bank Commissioner, 1942 (Box 12)
    - Blind, Board of Education of, 1942 (Box 12)
    - Boys, Conn. School For, 1942 (Box 12)
    - C (Miscellaneous), 1942 (Box 12)
    - Comptroller, 1942-1943 (Box 12)
    - Connecticut Regional Market Authority, 1942 (Box 12)
    - Connecticut State Farm For Women, 1942 (Box 12)
    - Connecticut State Hospital, 1942 (Box 12)
    - Connecticut State Prison, 1942 (Box 12)
    - Connecticut Wholesale Milk Producers Council, 1942 (Box 12)
    - County Commissioners, 1942 (Box 12)
    - D (Miscellaneous), 1942 (Box 12)
    - Dairy & Food Commission, 1942 (Box 12)
    - Dental Commission, 1942 (Box 12)
    - Development Commission, State, 1942 (Box 12)
    - Domestic Animals, 1942 (Box 12)
    - Education, Board Of, 1942 (Box 12)
    - Embalmers, Board of Examiners of, 1942 (Box 12)
    - Engineers & Land Surveyors, Professional, State Board of Registration For, 1942 (Box 12)
    - F (Miscellaneous), 1942 (Box 12)
    - Fairfield State Hospital, 1942 (Box 12)
    - Finance & Control, Board of, 1942 (Box 12)
    - Fish & Game Commission, 1942 (Box 12)
    - G (Miscellaneous), 1942 (Box 12)
    - Governor, 1942 (Box 12)
    - H (Miscellaneous) (1941 - 1942) (Box 12)
    - Harbor Masters, 1942 (Box 12)
    - Healing Arts, State Board of, 1942 (Box 12)
    - Health Department, 1942 (Box 12)
    - Highway Department File, 1942 (Box 12)
    - Highway Department (Matters Pertaining to Approvals), 1942 (Box 12)
    - Insurance Department, 1942 (Box 12)
    - Interstate Sanitation Commission, 1940-1942 (Box 12)
    - J (Miscellaneous), 1942 (Box 12)
    - Judiciary Department, 1942 (Box 12)
    - K (Miscellaneous), 1942 (Box 12)
    - Labor and Factory Inspection, 1942 (Box 12)
    - Library, 1942 (Box 12)
    - Liquor Control Commission, 1942 (Box 12)
    - Long Lane Farm, 1942 (Box 12)
    - M (Miscellaneous), 1942 (Box 12)
    - Mansfield State Training School & Hospital, 1942 (Box 12)
    - Mc (Miscellaneous), 1942 (Box 12)
    - Medical Examining Board, Conn., 1942 (Box 12)
    - Milk Administrator, 1942 (Box 12)
    - Motor Vehicle Department, 1942 (Box 12)
    - N (Miscellaneous), 1942 (Box 12)
    - Natureopathic, Board of, 1942 (Box 12)
    - Norwich State Hospital (1941 - 1942) (Box 12)
    - O (Miscellaneous), 1942 (Box 12)
    - Opticians Commission, 1942 (Box 12)
    - Osteopathic, Board Of Reg. & Examination, 1942 (Box 12)
    - P (Miscellaneous), 1942 (Box 12)
    - Park & Forest Commission, 1942 (Box 12)
    - Personnel Director, 1942 (Box 12)
    - Physic-Therapy Technicians, Board of Examiners for, 1942 (Box 13)
    - Police Department, State, 1942 (Box 13)
    - Public Utilities Commission, 1942 (Box 13)
    - Public Works Commission, 1942 (Box 13)
    - R (Miscellaneous), 1942 (Box 13)
    - Retirement Commission, 1942 (Box 13)
    - S (Miscellaneous), 1942 (Box 13)
    - Secretary of the State, 1941-1942 (Box 13)
    - Southbury Training School, 1942 (Box 13)
    - State Police Association, 1942 (Box 13)
    - Tax Commissioner, 1942 (Box 13)
    - Treasurer, State of Connecticut, 1942 (Box 13)
    - U (Miscellaneous), 1942 (Box 13)
    - University Of Connecticut, 1941-1942 (Box 13)
    - Voting, 1942 (Box 13)
    - W (Miscellaneous), 1942 (Box 13)
    - Water Commission, 1941-1942 (Box 13)
    - Welfare Department, 1942 (Box 13)
  - 1943
    - Adjutant General, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Agriculture Department, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Aeronautics Commission, 1943 (Box 14)
    - American Legion - Soldiers, Sailors & Marine Funds, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Attorneys General of Other States, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Auditors; State, 1943 (Box 14)
    - B (Miscellaneous), 1943 (Box 14)
    - Bank Commissioner, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Barbers, State Board Of Examiners of, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Board Of Accountancy, State, 1943 (Box 14)
    - C (Miscellaneous), 1943 (Box 14)
    - Cheshire Reformatory, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Chiropractic Examiners, State Board of, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Common Pleas Court - Constitutionality, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Comptroller, 1942-1943 (Box 14)
    - Connecticut State Hospital, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Connecticut State Housing Authority, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Connecticut State Prison, 1942 (Box 14)
    - Coroner, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Council of State Governments, 1942-1944 (Box 14)
    - County Commissioners, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Dairy & Food Commissioner, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Dental Commission, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Development Commission State, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Domestic Animals Commission, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Education, State Board of, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Engineers & Land Surveyors, State Board of Registration For, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Examiner of Public Records, 1943 (Box 14)
    - F (Miscellaneous), 1943 (Box 14)
    - Fairfield State Hospital, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Finance & Control, Board of, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Fish & Game Commission, 1943 (Box 14)
    - G (Miscellaneous), 1943 (Box 14)
    - Governor, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Health Department, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Highway, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Highway Awards, Acceptance of, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Insurance Department, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Intergovernmental Cooperation, Commission on, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Judiciary Department, 1943 (Box 14)
    - K (Miscellaneous), 1943 (Box 14)
    - L (Miscellaneous), 1943 (Box 14)
    - Labor & Factory Inspection, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Library, State, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Liquor Control Commission, 1943 (Box 14)
    - M (Miscellaneous), 1943 (Box 14)
    - Mansfield State Training School & Hospital, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Merritt Highway Commission, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Military, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Milk Administrator, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Motor Vehicle Department, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Natureopathic, Boards of, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Norwich State Hospital, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Osteopathic, Board Of Registration & Examiners, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Park & Forest Commission, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Personnel Director, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Police Department State, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Public Utilities Commission, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Public Works Commission, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Retirement Commission, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Secretary of State, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Sheriff, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Southbury Training School, 1943 (Box 14)
    - State Police Association, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Statue Revision Commission, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Tax Commissioner, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Teachers Retirement Board, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Traffic Commission, State, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Treasurer, State of Connecticut, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Tuberculosis Commission, State, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Undercliff Sanitarium, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Unemployment Compensation, 1943 (Box 14)
    - United States Government, 1943 (Box 14)
    - University of Connecticut, 1943 (Box 14)
    - War Council, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Water Commission, 1943-1944 (Box 14)
    - Welfare Department, 1943 (Box 14)
  - 1944
    - A (Miscellaneous), 1944 (Box 15)
    - Adjutant General, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Aeronautics Commission, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Agriculture, Department of, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Attorneys General of Other States, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Auditors, State, 1944 (Box 15)
    - B (Miscellaneous), 1944 (Box 15)
    - Bank Commissioner, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Barbers, State Board of Examiners of, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Blind, Board of Education of, 1943-1944 (Box 15)
    - C (Miscellaneous), 1944 (Box 15)
    - Cheshire Reformatory, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Comptroller, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Connecticut State Farm For Women, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Connecticut State Hospital, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Connecticut State Housing Authority, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Coroner, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Council of State Governments, 1944 (Box 15)
    - County Commissioners, 1944 (Box 15)
    - D (Miscellaneous), 1944 (Box 15)
    - Dental Commission, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Development Commission State, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Domestic Animals Commission, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Education, State Board, 1942-1944 (Box 15)
    - Election, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Embalmers, Board of Examiners of, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Engineers & Land Surveyors, State Board of Registration for, 1944 (Box 15)
    - F (Miscellaneous), 1943-1944 (Box 15)
    - Fairfield State Hospital, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Finance & Control, Commission of, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Fish & Game Commission, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Governor, 1944 (Box 15)
    - H (Miscellaneous), 1944 (Box 15)
    - Healing Arts, State Board of, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Health Department, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Highway, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Insurance Department, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Interstate Sanitation Commission, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Judicial Department, State, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Justice, Department of, 1944 (Box 15)
    - K (Miscellaneous), 1944 (Box 15)
    - L (Miscellaneous), 1944 (Box 15)
    - Labor & Factory Inspection, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Liquor Control Commission, 1942-1944 (Box 15)
    - Long Lane Farm, 1944 (Box 15)
    - M (Miscellaneous), 1944 (Box 15)
    - Mansfield State Training School & Hospital, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Merritt Parkway Commission, 1942-1944 (Box 15)
    - Military, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Milk Administrator, 1943-1944 (Box 15)
    - Mosquito Control, State Board Of, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Motor Vehicle Department, 1944 (Box 15)
    - N (Miscellaneous), 1944 (Box 15)
    - Norwich State Hospital, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Nursing, Board Of Examiners of, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Opticians Commission, 1943 (Box 15)
    - Optometry, Board of, 1944 (Box 15)
    - P (Miscellaneous), 1944 (Box 15)
    - Park & Forest Commission, State, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Personnel Director, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Pharmacy, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Probate Court, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Public Utilities Commission, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Public Welfare Council, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Purchases, Supervisor of, 1944 (Box 15)
    - R (Miscellaneous), 1944 (Box 15)
    - Retirement Commission, 1943-1944 (Box 15)
    - S (Miscellaneous), 1944 (Box 15)
    - Secretary of State, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Soldiers, Sailors, & Marines Fund, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Southbury Training School, 1944-1945 (Box 15)
    - State Police Association, 1944 (Box 15)
    - State Police Department, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Tax Commissioner, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Teachers Retirement Board, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Town Clerk, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Traffic Commission, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Treasurer, State, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Tuberculosis Commission, State, 1944 (Box 15)
    - U (Miscellaneous), 1944 (Box 16)
    - Undercliff Sanitarium, 1944 (Box 16)
    - Unemployment Compensation, 1944 (Box 16)
    - University of Connecticut, 1944 (Box 16)
    - U.S. Department of Justice, 1944 (Box 16)
    - V (Miscellaneous), 1944 (Box 16)
    - Voting, 1944 (Box 16)
    - W (Miscellaneous), 1944 (Box 16)
    - War Orders, 1943 (Box 16)
    - Water Commission, 1943-1944 (Box 16)
    - Welfare Compromises, 1944 (Box 16)
    - Welfare Department, 1942-1944 (Box 16)
    - Welfare Uncollectibles, 1944 (Box 16)
    - X-Z (Miscellaneous), 1944 (Box 16)
  - 1945
    - A (Miscellaneous), 1945 (Box 16)
    - Adjutant General, 1945 (Box 16)
    - Aeronautics Commission, 1945 (Box 16)
    - Agriculture, Department of, 1945 (Box 16)
    - Attorney’s General of Other States, 1945 (Box 16)
    - Auditors, State, 1945 (Box 16)
    - B (Miscellaneous), 1945 (Box 16)
    - Bank Commissioner, 1945 (Box 16)
    - Blind, Board of Education of, 1945 (Box 16)
    - C (Miscellaneous), 1945 (Box 16)
    - Cheshire Reformatory, 1945 (Box 16)
    - Compensation Commissioner, 1943-1945 (Box 16)
    - Comptroller, 1945 (Box 16)
    - Connecticut State Hospital, 1944 (Box 16)
    - Dairy & Food Commission, 1945 (Box 16)
    - Dental Commission, 1945 (Box 16)
    - Domestic Animals Commission, 1945 (Box 16)
    - E (Miscellaneous), 1945 (Box 16)
    - Education, State Board of, 1944-1945 (Box 16)
    - Election, 1944-1945 (Box 16)
    - Embalmers, Board Of Examiners, 1945 (Box 16)
    - Engineers & Land Surveyors, State Board of Registration of, 1945 (Box 16)
    - F (Miscellaneous), 1945 (Box 16)
    - Fairfield State Hospital, 1945 (Box 16)
    - Finance & Control, Commissioner of, 1945 (Box 16)
    - Fish & Game Commission, 1945 (Box 16)
    - Fuel Administrator, 1945 (Box 16)
    - G (Miscellaneous), 1945 (Box 16)
    - General Assembly, 1945 (Box 16)
    - Governor, 1945 (Box 16)
    - H (Miscellaneous), 1945 (Box 16)
    - Health Department, 1944-1945 (Box 16)
    - Highway Condemnation Approvals under $1,000, 1945 (Box 16)
    - Highway Department, 1945 (Box 16)
    - Insurance Department, 1945 (Box 17)
    - Judicial Department State, 1945 (Box 17)
    - L (Miscellaneous), 1944-1945 (Box 17)
    - Labor & Factory Inspection, 1945 (Box 17)
    - Laurel Heights Sanitarium, 1945 (Box 17)
    - Library, State, 1945 (Box 17)
    - Liquor Control Commission, 1944-1945 (Box 17)
    - M (Miscellaneous), 1945 (Box 17)
    - Mansfield State Training School & Hospital, 1945 (Box 17)
    - Meditation & Arbitration, State Board of, 1945 (Box 17)
    - Medical Examining Board, 1945 (Box 17)
    - Merritt Parkway Commission, 1945 (Box 17)
    - Milk Administrator, 1945 (Box 17)
    - Motor Vehicles Department, 1945 (Box 17)
    - Mystic Oral School for the Deaf, 1945 (Box 17)
    - Natureopathic, State Board of, 1945 (Box 17)
    - Norwich State Hospital, 1945 (Box 17)
    - Nurses Examining Board, 1945 (Box 17)
    - Optician’s Commission, 1945 (Box 17)
    - Osteopathic, Board of Registration & Examination, 1945 (Box 17)
    - P (Miscellaneous), 1945 (Box 17)
    - Park & Forest Commission, 1945 (Box 17)
    - Personnel Director, 1945 (Box 17)
    - Police Department, State, 1945 (Box 17)
    - Public Personnel Committee, 1945 (Box 17)
    - Public Utilities Commission, 1945 (Box 17)
    - R (Miscellaneous), 1945 (Box 17)
    - Retirement Commission, 1945 (Box 17)
    - S (Miscellaneous), 1945 (Box 17)
    - Secretary of the State, 1945 (Box 17)
    - Shell Fish Commission, 1945 (Box 17)
    - Sheriff, 1945 (Box 17)
    - Soldiers, Sailors, & Marines Fund, 1945 (Box 17)
    - Southbury Training School, 1944 (Box 17)
    - State Police Association, 1945 (Box 17)
    - T (Miscellaneous), 1945 (Box 17)
    - Tax Commissioner, 1944-1945 (Box 17)
    - Teachers Retirement Board, 1945 (Box 17)
    - Treasurer, State, 1945 (Box 17)
    - Tuberculosis Commission, State, 1944-1945 (Box 17)
    - University of Connecticut, 1944-1945 (Box 17)
    - U.S. Government, 1945 (Box 17)
    - Veterans Home Commission, 1945 (Box 17)
    - Voting, 1945 (Box 17)
    - W (Miscellaneous), 1945 (Box 17)
    - War Orders, 1945-1946 (Box 17)
    - Water Commission, 1945 (Box 17)
    - Welfare Compromises, 1945 (Box 17)
    - Welfare Department, 1944-1945 (Box 17)
    - Welfare Files returned to Mr. Putney, 1945 (Box 17)
    - Welfare Uncollectibles, 1945 (Box 17)
    - X-Z, 1945 (Box 17)
  - 1946
    - A (Miscellaneous), 1945-1946 (Box 18)
    - Adjutant General, 1946 (Box 18)
    - Aeronautics Commission, 1946 (Box 18)
    - Agriculture, Department of, 1946 (Box 18)
    - Airport Commission, 1946 (Box 18)
    - Alcoholism, Commission on, 1946 (Box 18)
    - Attorneys General of Other States, 1944-1946 (Box 18)
    - Auditors, State, 1946 (Box 18)
    - Bank Commissioner, 1945-1946 (Box 18)
    - Barbers, State Board of Examiners of, 1946 (Box 18)
    - Beach Erosion Control Committee, Conn., 1946 (Box 18)
    - Budget, Director of the, 1946 (Box 18)
    - C (Miscellaneous), 1946 (Box 18)
    - Chiropode, Board of Examiners, 1946 (Box 18)
    - Chiropractic Examiners, State Board of, 1946 (Box 18)
    - Compromises & Cancellations (Other then Welfare Department), 1946 (Box 18)
    - Comptroller, 1946 (Box 18)
    - Connecticut Regional Marketing Authority, 1946 (Box 18)
    - Connecticut State Hospital, 1946 (Box 18)
    - Country Commissioners, 1946 (Box 18)
    - Dairy & Food Commission, 1946 (Box 18)
    - Dental Commission, 1946 (Box 18)
    - Education, State Board of, 1946 (Box 18)
    - Election Matters, 1946 (Box 18)
    - Engineer & Land Surveyors, State Board of Registration of, 1946 (Box 18)
    - Fairfield State Hospital, 1946 (Box 18)
    - Finance & Control, Commissioner of, 1946 (Box 18)
    - Fish & Game Commission, 1946 (Box 18)
    - Flood Control & Water Policy Commission, 1946 (Box 18)
    - Foreclosures, (Misc), 1945-1946 (Box 18)
    - Forest & Wild Life, Conn. Commission on, 1946 (Box 18)
    - General Assembly, 1946 (Box 18)
    - Governor, 1946 (Box 18)
    - Health Department, 1946 (Box 18)
    - Highway Department - April, May, June, 1946 (Box 18)
    - Housing Authority, Conn. State, 1946 (Box 18)